To sum up, there are four things I
want you to remember.
Firstly, there are two formats of labelling a
map or diagram.
The steps for these two are quite similar.
Secondly, making predictions before you listen is really
important.
It helps you listen in an active and
attentive way.
The more accurate your predictions about paraphrases are,
the more actively you will listen to them.
Thirdly, never leave your answer sheet blank because
you won't lose points if you write the
incorrect answers.
Lastly, continue to expand your vocabulary.
Alright, I hope you guys study hard and
achieve your goal
in the near future.
For now, goodbye and see you in the next
lesson.